What was the entire incident and
last night in the area for 350 2 1/2 hours there were
announcements of a person being injured
in which he was rescued from a forest area of ​​Taj Mahal Upper village
and
sent to the hospital, from there he was
referred to Bansal Hospital, after talking to him it was
found out that the names of two accused are one Hansraj and
one Aditya, both of them injured him and
left him in the forest and after that they
ran away from there, they kept his mobile with them and
called his man for ransom, his
man picked up the phone and told him that
if he is worried about the life of his son, then hand him over to
us, after this there was no
contact between these two, after
knowing the names of these two accused,
we have started investigation,
today it has come to light that the
maternal uncle of the boy had made this entire plan,
your maternal uncle has a good influence in the family,
he is well aware of the family's property, bank balance
and all other things,
hence he made this plan in
connivance with these two and
hired both of them as handsman and
planned to make him escape and leave him in the forest.  These people had made 1 lakh rupees. The investigation done so far has
revealed that there was
no such plan to kill him. Their plan was to
injure him and leave him in the forest
and till then recover the money from the family. The
money was to be recovered
because obviously the name of the uncle is
his maternal uncle. He had planned to move from here today.
There is information
that he had booked some tickets as well
but we have not got complete clarity about that either. At present,
we have
arrested the uncle a short while ago.
He is sleeping in the
hotel. Three people have been arrested. The
main accused who was involved in the fight yesterday and the
uncle who was involved in planning are all three
arrested. There is
no information about the uncle's background yet.
It has been told for the first time that the uncle works
in partnership with some of their builders.
Sir, these accused are
also helping him for travelling.
One of the accused, Hansraj,
knows his uncle and was also with him in making the plan. So
yesterday when his man received a
call for ransom, he again called him.  The
man was left in the forest and taken to his maternal uncle's house. His maternal uncle,
his mother and another sister
all went together to Thane to lodge a report.
Meanwhile, when Thane came to
know about the complaint of this child at night,
they
made a report about it in MP Nagar Thane.